&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们编写的JavaScript代码必须在浏览器中执行。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: The JavaScript code that
we write has to execute in the browser.
为了做到这一点，我们需要知道一点关于网页是如何创建和
In order that, we need to know a little
bit about how web pages are created and
它们实际上是如何呈现的，以及它们如何使用界面更新。
how they're actually rendered, and
how they use interface updates.
所以让我们来谈谈网页是如何诞生的。
So let's talk e a little bit
about how web pages are born.
同样，第一步是浏览器向服务器发送GET请求，
Again, the step one is the browser goes
ahead sends get request to a server,
他说，嘿，给我一个网页。
he says, hey, give me a webpage.
我们得到回复，猜猜里面有什么？
We get back a response and
guess what it has in it?
网页，就像典型的HTML一样。
A webpage, like typically HTML.
HTML只是文本的一个很大的刺，可能还有我们需要的其他东西
The HTML is just a big sting of text and
likely has other things that we need to
比如样式表、JavaScript文件等等，对吗？
get like Style Sheets, JavaScript files,
so on and so forth, right?
成为我们正在创建的网页的基础。
Becomes the basis of the webpage
that we're creating.
HTML还需要解析和
That HTML also needs to parsed and
弄清楚这个页面的实际结构是什么，对吧？
figure out like what is the actual
structure of this page, right?
所以我们把HTML解析成一个叫做文档的东西
So we take the HTML and we pars it
into this thing called the document
对象模型，DOM，如果你愿意的话，每个人的朋友。
object model, the DOM if you will,
everyone's friend.
它基本上是从文档开始的页面表示。
Which is basically the representation
of the page starting with the document.
我们得到了HTML标记，头部和主体，等等。
We got the HTML tag, the head and
the body, so on and so forth.
这是一个像大树一样的结构
It's this big tree like structure
这是我们拥有的网页的表示。
that is a representation of
the webpage that we have.
现在前面的例子中，我们看到了获取一些CSS的链接。
Now in the previous example,
we saw that link to go get some CSS.
我们也需要去拿那个。
We need to go fetch that as well.
这显然是一种不同的语言，如果你愿意的话，对吧？
That's obviously a different language,
if you will, right?
而这需要某种程度上的创造，
And that needs to kind of get created,
找出此页面的所有样式规则是什么？
figure out what are all
the styling rules for this page?
它变成了另一个非常相似的原型，叫做CSS对象
And that gets turned into this other very
similar archetype called the CSS object
模特。
model.
所以级联风格的形状对象模型，这是一个大嘴巴。
So the cascading style shape object model,
that's a mouthful.
它基本上就是一棵巨大的树，包含了所有的规则
Which is just basically a giant
tree of all the rules for
我们的页面应该是什么样子。
how our page should look.
在一种情况下，我们有一个完整的网页结构或
So we have in one case is we have
an entire structure of how the web page or
Web应用程序布局。
web application is laid out.
我们还有另一个
And we've got this other one for
一套关于不同事物应该看起来如何不同的规则，对吧？
a set of rules on how different
things should look, right?
这不一定是每个特定元素看起来的样子，
That's not necessarily how
each particular element looks,
但我们要去告诉所有的段落标签。
but we're gonna go tell
all paragraph tags.
所有的事情都很酷，对吧？
All things with the class of cool, right?
这不是语义上的，但我们会遵循它。
That's not semantic, but we'll go with it.
以及我们是如何制定这些规则的。
And how we have all these rules.
我们有这样的世界状况，对吧？
We have that state of the world, right?
所以为了弄清楚页面看起来是什么样子，我们必须获取状态
So in order to figure out what the page
looks like we have to take the state of
世界和关于世界的规则
the world and
the rules about the world and
我们把它们放在一个叫做渲染树的东西里。
we put them together into this
thing called the render tree.
现在你会注意到渲染树，比如，我们不再有那个HTML了，
Now the render tree you'll notice like,
we don't have that HTML anymore and
我们没有头，对吧？
we don't have the head, right?
只有那些部件才会真正出现在页面上，对吧？
It's only the parts that will
actually show up on the page, right?
因为我们不需要担心如何设计我们不会展示的东西，
Because we don't need to worry about how
to style things we're not going to show,
对吧？
right?
所以基本上我们页面的结构以及计算规则。
So basically the structure of our
page along with the computive rules.
它把所有的CSS和所有的规则都搞清楚了
It take all the CSS and
all the rules and figure it all out and
告诉我DOM这一部分的给定元素应该是什么样子，以及
tell me what this given element on this
part of the DOM should look like, and
另一个给定的元素，等等。
this other given element,
so on and so forth.
所以渲染树，再一次，
So the render tree, again,
与页面上的可见对象具有一对一的映射。
has a one-to-one mapping with
the visible objects on the page.
可以将多个规则应用于同一元素。
You can have multiple rules
applied to the same element.
可以将一个规则应用于多个元素。
You could have one rule
applied to multiple elements.
当涉及到渲染树时，
When it comes to the render tree,
这里是所有要显示在页面上的内容。
it's here are all the things that
are gonna show up on the page.
这是他们应该看起来的样子，非常酷。
Here's what they should look like,
very cool.
任何隐藏的东西都不会显示出来，就像你没有显示一样，
Things that anything hidden is not
gonna show like if you do display none,
这不在渲染树上，因为我们不显示它。
that's not on the render tree,
cuz we're not displaying it.
头的事情不会发生。
Things with the head are not gonna happen.
但是像伪元素这样的东西，嘿，把另一个元素放在前面
But things like pseudo elements like,
hey, put this other element before
这另一个，我们写在CSS中，那是在渲染树上。
this other one and we write that in CSS,
that is on the render tree.
所以有点不同
So it's a little bit different.
我们需要把这一切都搞清楚。
And we need to figure that all out.
我们计算出来的过程叫做风格计算。
And the process that we figure that
out is called style calculation.
浏览器查看所有样式和所有元素。
The browser looks at all the styles and
all of the elements.
它找出了应用于这个给定元素的样式。
It figures out what styles
apply to this given element.
适用什么规则？
What rules apply?
好的，两条规则改变了背景颜色，
Okay, two rules are changing
out the background color,
哪一个赢了，对吧？
which one of these win, right?
把它看起来的一切都搞清楚了。
And kind of figures out
everything about how it looks.
所以再一次，这确实导致了两件事。
So again,
this really results in two things.
例如，应用哪些规则，如果两个规则定义相同的属性两次，
Like, which rules apply and if two rules
are defining the same property twice,
哪一个赢了，哪一个有更高的特异性？
which one wins,
which one has higher specificity?
如果它们具有相同的特异性，那么哪个更晚？
If they have the same specificity,
which one came later?
等等。
So on and so forth.
浏览器会发现所有这些，你只要给它一个基本的结构，
The browser will figure that all out,
you just basically give it a structure,
给它一些关于结构的规则，[声音]。
give it some rules about that structure,
[SOUND].
出现一个渲染托盘，准备显示在页面上。
Out comes a render tray ready
to be shown onto the page.
这并不一定会在页面上显示出来，但是
That doesn't necessarily
show it on the page, but
这就像是这一页上的一组说明？
that is like a set of instructions
on what's on this page?
它看起来像什么？
What does it look like?
我们必须记住的另一件事是弄清楚哪些规则适用？
The other thing that we have to keep in
mind is figuring out which rules apply?
因为这可能有点棘手，对吧？
Cuz it can be a little bit tricky, right?
我们可以让CSS中的所有P规则适用于段落，很好。
We could have stuff like all P rules
in CSS apply to the paragraphs, fine.
我们也可以有一些稍微复杂一点的，
We could also have some
a slightly more complicated one,
就像第n个孩子4n-1，对吗？
like nth child 4n- 1, right?
这需要更多的工作才能弄明白。
That takes a little more
work to figure out.
[笑]这并不像这样简单，你是一个段落还是
[LAUGH] That's not as simple as like,
are you a paragraph or
任何沿着这条线的东西。
anything along those lines.
我们得做些工作才能弄明白，对吧？
We have to do work to figure that out,
right?
你几乎可以看到这里的发展方向，
You can almost see where
this is going here,
这是我们必须做更多工作的事情，往往需要更长的时间。
which is things where we have to do more
work tend to take a little bit longer.
所以你做的选择器越复杂，
So the more complicated you
end up making your selectors,
整个过程需要的时间就越长。
the longer this whole
process is going to take.
看起来电脑很快而且所有东西都是免费的，
It seems like computers are fast and
everything is free,
但事实并非如此。
but that's not really the case.
我们做的每一件事都需要一些时间，
Everything we go ahead and
do is gonna take some amount of time,
而且做这件事需要的工作越多，花费的时间也就越多。
and the more work it takes to do it,
the more time it takes.
所以简单的经验法则，类名是超级简单的。
So easy rule of thumb,
class names are super simple.
比如，这有页眉或页脚之类的类吗？
Like, does this have the class of
header or footer, or whatever?
这是一个是或不是的问题。
That's a yes or no question.
这很容易弄明白。
That's very easy to figure out.
但是当我们到达侧边栏页面的时候，
But when we get to the point where
it's going off the page of sidebar,
菜单项的第一个后代，第n个孩子，这需要更长的时间。
the first descendant of menu-item,
the nth-child, that takes a lot longer.
因此，如果可能，您总是可以加快计算所有样式和
So when possible you can always speed up
the time of calculating all the styles and
通过保持尽可能简单来匹配元素，对吗？
matching to the elements by keeping
it as simple as possible, right?
使用类名定义它的任何类型的系统都是BEM或CSS，
Any kind of system where you define it
with class names would be BEM or CSS,
这真的无关紧要，对吧？
it doesn't really matter, right?
但是如果你可以通过定义所有这些状态和类来做到这一点，
But if you can do this by defining
all those states and classes,
总比耍花招快，对吧？
it is always gonna be faster
than doing trickery, right?
因为浏览器读取选择器，如果有一个选择器很酷，
Because the browsers they read the
selectors, if there's one selector cool,
他们准备好出发了。
they're ready to go.
否则，他们必须做更多的计算。
Otherwise, they have to
do more computation.
选择器越少，速度就越快，对吧？
The less selectors,
the faster is going to be, right?
它可以是这样的东西，我需要每隔一排，对吗？
And it could be stuff like well,
I need every fourth row, right?
很酷，但它确实提出了问题。
Very cool, but it does raise the question.
如果你需要用它，就用它。
If you need to use it, use it.
但是如果你说，嘿，我正在从服务器生成这个巨大的表，
But if you're like, hey, I'm generating
this giant table from the server,
服务器是否可以为每四行添加正确的类名，对吗？
can the server put the right class
name on for every fourth row, right?
很酷，然后你可以加快用户浏览器必须做的事情，或者
Cool, then you can speed up what
the user's browser has to do, or
如果你运输的是反应堆，角，或余烬，而且
if you're shipping reactor,
angular, or ember anyway, and
你有一些逻辑，你可以把类放在每隔四行，对吗？
you have some logic in there and you can
put the class on every fourth row, right?
你已经在经历这个过程了。
You're already going through that process.
你最好在那里做，而不是加载额外的工作
You might as well do it there
than loading extra work
到选择器引擎上来找出它。
onto the selector engine to figure it out.
所以我们设计风格，找出适用的规则，然后
So we style,
we figure out what the rules apply, and
然后我们试着把它们放在一起。
then we kind of try to
put them all together.
选择器匹配只需要，好的，这是n中的第四行加1减4。
Selector matching just takes, okay, this
is the fourth row in the n plus 1 minus 4.
它确实有一类非常重要的表行，并计算所有这些。
It does have a class of very important
table row and figuring all that.
当多个选择器应用于一个元素时，
When multiple selectors
apply to an element,
浏览器需要找出谁赢了。
the browser needs to figure out who wins.
显然，加快速度的最快方法就是不去做。
And obviously, the fastest way to
speed that up is not to do it.
所以再一次，如果你可以通过某种方式来命名你的
So again, if you can do this by having
some kind of way that you're naming your
CSS类对所有这些进行描述并测试对象的实际状态，
CSS classes that figures all that and
tests the actual state of the object,
会更快，对吧？
it's going to be faster, right?
我会非常诚实的，尽管，&gt；&gt；steve kinney：风格失效，
I'm gonna be really honest though like,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Style invalidation,
穿上或脱下东西并不重要。
taking stuff on or
off doesn't matter as much.
这将永远是一个相对较短的部分。
And this will always be
a relatively short part.
如果你注意到，如果你测量计算样式是一个非常重要的部分，
If you notice, if you measure that
calculating styles is a very big part,
当您等待加载初始页面时。
as you wait for the initial page to load.
这些是要寻找的地方，当我们看到其他一些地方时，我的怀疑
These are the places to look for,
my suspicion when we saw some of the other
正在进行的事情是，它可能不是获得初始页面的最长时间。
things going on is it's probably not
the longest for getting the initial page.
解析JavaScript可能是最长的，但有很多这样的规则
Parsing the JavaScript is probably the
longest, but a lot of the kind of rules
从渲染以及如何优化渲染性能，都与以下事实有关
from rendering and how to optimize render
performance, has to do with the fact that
JavaScript代码可能会在第一次加载后更改页面。
JavaScript code is likely gonna change
the page after that first load.
我们怎么做事情，我们怎么做重复的事情，对吗？
And how do we do stuff,
how do we do repeated stuff, right?
如果你想到一部动画，
If you think about an animation,
动画就像他们可能会多次改变页面，对吧？
an animation is like they're changing
the page many times possibly, right?
就像很多事情都归结为一个页面已经被加载了，但这是值得的
And like a lot of it comes down to one
page has been loaded, but it's worthwhile
测量是否在初始加载时看到，计算样式是永远需要的。
measuring if you see on initial load,
calculating the styles is taking forever.
这些是要下去的路径，或者您确实有非常复杂的选择器。
These are the kind of paths to go down or
you do have very complicated selectors.
你是不是有一堆不用的CSS，对吧？
Do you have a bunch of CSS
that you're not using, right?
如果你有一堆不使用的CSS，我们仍然需要检查，对吗？
If you have a bunch of CSS that you're not
using, we still have to check that, right?
将代码从代码库中取出将有助于解决这个问题，对吗？
Getting that code out of your code base
is going to help with that issue, right?
我们稍后会看一些工具，比如自动化，所以
And we'll look at some tools later for
like automating that, so
你不需要用手，看，CSS类。
you don't have to hand,
look, the CSS class.
我想知道它是不是在任何元素上，对吗？
I wonder if it's on any elements, right?
就像好运不会搞砸一样。
Like good luck not messing that up.
因此，就像拥有某种自动化工具一样，它通常是非常有用的。
So like having some kind of like automated
tool it does it is usually really useful.
因此，在失速计算部分的高水平是减少未使用的CSS的数量
So the high level on stall calculation
part is reduce the amount of unused CSS
你要运输的。
the you're shipping.
你拥有的风格越少，需要检查的东西就越少。
The less styles you have,
the less there is to check.
并试图减少影响给定元素的样式的数量
And trying to reduce the number of
styles that effect a given element
通过使用某种可以将内容归结为一个类的系统，对吗？
by using some kind of system that can
boil stuff down to one class, right?
如果你能把这两件事做好，这两件事恰好是有用的
If you can pull those two things off,
those happen to be useful for
还有很多其他的事情，对吧？
a number of other things too, right?
它碰巧很有用，因为这样，不仅浏览器要做的事情更少，
It happens to be useful, cuz like, not
only is that less for the browser to do,
但你通过电线发送的东西也少了，对吧？
but it's also less stuff you're
sending over the wire, right?
对于很多东西来说，它也更容易管理自己的代码库。
It's also, for a lot of the stuff,
easier to manage your own code base.
这些CSS系统，如BEM和CSS，最初并不一定是为
These CSS systems, like BEM and CSS,
were not necessarily originally built for
表演。
performance.
它们是为开发者的理智而设计的，[笑]对吗？
They were built for
developer sanity, [LAUGH] right?
只是碰巧是系统
It just happens to be that systems for
开发人员的理智还可以使您的代码更快。
developer sanity also
make your code faster.
所以一定要注意其中之一。
So definitely kind of look out for
one of those.
好的，在我们弄清楚样式和渲染树之后，然后
All right, so after we figure out
the styles and the render tree, and
我们这整棵树的东西都准备好了，对吧？
we have this entire tree of
stuff ready to go, right?
我们知道页面上将要出现的一切。
We know everything that's
gonna be on the page.
我们有一些关于每件事应该是什么样子的规则。
We have some rules about what
everything should look like.
是时候真正把它放在页面上了，对吧？
It's time to actually put it on the page,
right?
我们将在一秒钟内更深入地讨论这个问题。
And we’re gonna go into this one
a little more in depth in a second.
我们将完成所有其他步骤，并且
We’re gonna go through
all the other steps, and
然后我们再回到那个问题上。
then we’re gonna round back to that.
但这比看起来要棘手，对吧？
But this is trickier than it seems, right?
你必须基本上找出每个元素的大小，
You have to basically find out
the size of every element,
当你会打破一条新的线，一切之间的关系，对吗？
when you would break to a new line, the
relationship between everything, right?
这一点都不奇怪，这很复杂，而且需要一段时间，对吧？
It should be no surprise that this is
complicated, and it takes a while, right?
不过，我们稍后会回到这个问题上。
We will round back to this
in a little bit though.
所以你知道这些元素是什么样子的。
So you know what the elements look like.
你知道他们在页面上的位置。
You know where they go on the page.
是时候去做了，对吧？
It's time to make them, right?
所以在绘画的过程中，你会得到所有关于它看起来像什么的信息，
So the process of painting, you take all
the information about what it looks like,
您可以获取有关其去向的信息，这些信息会多次影响大小
you take the information about where it
goes which a lot of times affects the size
对吧？
of it, right?
就像它将是宽度的50%。
Like it's gonna be 50% of the width.
嗯，在你知道有多少像素之前，你必须布局页面，对吗？
Well, you gotta lay out the page before
you know how many pixels that is, right?
一旦你弄清楚了所有事情的走向并弄明白了所有的规则，
Once you've figured out where everything
goes and have all the rules figured out,
然后你就可以继续画了。
then you can go ahead and paint.
这基本上意味着采用这个元素，对，这是一系列规则和
Which basically means take this element,
right, which is a bunch of rules and
定位数据，然后把它变成一张别人可以看到的图片，对吗？
location data, and turn it into
a picture that somebody can see, right?
这就是把它变成位图图像的过程，对吗？
So that's the process of like turning
it into a bitmap image, right?
所以它从一棵树和所有的东西就像一张图片。
So it goes from a tree and
all the stuff to like a picture.
你还没完全完，对吧？
You're not totally done yet, right?
你有照片。
You have pictures.
有照片并不一定能完成工作，对吧？
Having pictures does not necessarily
get the job done, right?
在你拿到照片后
After you have the pictures,
你需要将它们实际发送到GPU以便放到屏幕上，对吗？
you need to actually send them to the GPU
in order to be put onto the screen, right?
关于这一点有一些规则，我们稍后会谈到。
And there's some rules about this that
we'll kind of talk about in a little bit.
一旦做到这一点，你就准备好在互联网上赚取数百万美元
And once that, then you're ready
to just make Internet millions and
你可以走了。
you're good to go.